Concise Oxford Thesaurus

Number of headings / entries: 17068 / 17048
Version: 1.0 (06.04.2010)

Sourse: Babylon, Oxford University Press, Editor: Maurice Waite (Creation Date: 18.11.2004, Last Updated: 29.03.2006)

Description: This new edition of the Concise Oxford Thesaurus provides comprehensive, reliable help for all writing needs and crossword solving. The 365,000 synonyms and antonyms listed include unusual and specialist vocabulary as well as everyday words, and there is clear labelling of informal, dialect, literary and technical items. There are also 1000s of example sentences, and over 400 thematic lists provide information on a wide range of subjects.
(c) 2005 by Wiley Publishing, Inc., Cleveland, Ohio
